Most of us want to be in peak physical condition, get in shape and be healthy.
我们大多数人都希望处于身体的最佳状态、体型匀称且健康。
While some gym bunnies are more obsessed with looking ripped, for many of us nutrition and watching what you eat is a vital way to stay healthy.
虽然有些健身爱好者更痴迷于练出线条分明的肌肉，但对我们很多人来说，注重营养和饮食是保持健康的关键方式。
But when it comes to food, what is calorie counting, and what are the positives and negatives of it?
不过说到饮食，什么是卡路里计算？这种方式又有哪些利弊呢？
A law in the UK came into force in April 2022 that requires large businesses such as restaurants, takeaways, and cafes to display the calorie information of non-pre-packed food and soft drinks on their menus.
英国于2022年4月实施了一项法律，要求餐厅、外卖店、咖啡馆等大型商家，必须在菜单上标注非预包装食品和软饮的卡路里含量。
It’s a strategy aimed to tackle obesity and give people a more informed choice of what goes down their gullets.
这是一项旨在应对肥胖问题的策略，能让人们在选择入口食物时，做出更明智的选择。
According to the NHS (National Health Service), generally, the recommended daily intake of calories for male adults is 2,500 per day, while female adults should consume 2,000 to maintain their weight levels.
英国国家医疗服务体系（NHS）指出，通常情况下，为了维持体重水平，成年男性每日推荐卡路里摄入量为2500大卡，成年女性为2000大卡。
For those of us who wish to drop a few pounds, experts advise us to consume fewer calories than the recommended daily number, eat a balanced diet, and increase our levels of physical activity.
对于想要减重的人，专家建议摄入的卡路里应低于每日推荐量，同时要均衡饮食、增加运动量。
Being able to count calories and know how much we can eat is a great way to try and stay on track with our diet.
学会计算卡路里，清楚自己能吃多少，是帮助我们坚持饮食计划的有效方法。
However, there are some sceptics when it comes to calorie counting.
不过，也有一些人对卡路里计算持怀疑态度。
200 calories of fresh fruit and 200 calories of junk food, for example cookies, have the same caloric value. However, there is a question of the health benefits of what you’re consuming, regardless of calories.
比如200大卡的新鲜水果和200大卡的垃圾食品（例如饼干），卡路里数值相同，但两者的健康益处却天差地别。
While fresh fruit like apples contains things like vitamin C, junk food could contain an unhealthy level of sugar and fats.
像苹果这样的新鲜水果富含维生素C等营养物质，而垃圾食品往往含有过量有害健康的糖分和脂肪。
Likewise, fruit may fill you up and leave you not craving more food for longer than a biscuit with equal calories – meaning, overall, you eat less.
同样，同等卡路里的情况下，吃水果比吃饼干更容易让人产生饱腹感，并且饱腹感持续的时间更长，这意味着总体摄入的食物会更少。
Simply counting calories, while useful for weight loss, doesn’t take into account your intake of good fats, carbohydrates, and proteins – things that your body needs.
单纯的卡路里计算虽然对减重有帮助，但却没有考虑到身体所需的健康脂肪、碳水化合物和蛋白质的摄入量。
So, if you’re trying to stick to a low-carb diet, just looking at numbers of calories on a menu won’t be that useful.
因此，如果你正尝试坚持低碳水饮食，只看菜单上的卡路里数值并没有太大用处。
So, always be mindful that what you’re eating is part of a healthy balanced diet.
所以，一定要记住，你吃的食物必须是健康均衡饮食的一部分。